

Personal Information

Nationality: Bangladeshi Birth: August 21th, 1991

NID: 734874099

Language: Bangla, English **Skype Name:** mr.moshiurleon

Skills

Basic: C, PHP, MySQL, HTML,

CSS, JavaScript/JQuery

Application: MS Office, MS

Excel, Power Point

IDE: Dreamweaver, XAMPP

Project Management: Skype

OS: Windows

Additional Skills

- Knowledge in Health
- Martial Ar
- Leadership
- Analytical Ininking

Reference

Sr. Software Engineer in BJIT LTE 01912271635

Moshiur Rahman

Phone 01911368735

E-mail moshiur.leon21@gmail.com

Address House #114, Utter Para, Dorji Bari, Khilkhet, Word #17, Dhaka, 1229

Objective

To experience the joy of the tech world by working with a magnificent software team.

To work on my interest field, I attend a Post Graduate Diploma in Information and Communication Technology. Also completed BHMS from Dhaka University which is equivalent to BSc.

Project

 Online Admission System by Advanced Web Technology with Programming (PHP, MYSQL)

Work History

Jun 2018 - Current	National Karate Coach Bangladesh Karate Federation
Jun 2016 - Mar 2021	Homeopathic medicine consultant Nurse Home Center, Mirpur #6, Dhaka
Jun 2015 – May 2016	Trainee Doctor Govt. Homeopathic Medical College & Hospital, Dhaka

Education

Mar 2020 – August 2021	Post Graduate Diploma in Information and Communication Technology: (BKIICT) Long Course Batch 38
	Bangladesh Computer Council
Jan 2011 - Dec 2015	BHMS (Bachelor of Homeopathic Medicine And Surgery): Homeopathic Medicine.
	University Of Dhaka (Govt. Homeopathic Medical College &

Hospital)